Guide to the Duke University Chapel Recordings, 1954-2002 UA.17.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Recordings, 1954-2002; 1
  - Debra K. Brazzel - "To Stand in Awe", 1996 June 02; 2042
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0478)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - Sermon Untitled, 1996 June 09; 2043
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0811)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0479)
  - Karen Westerfield Tucker - Sermon Untitled, 1996 June 16; 2044
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0812)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0480)
  - Carlton P. Minnick, Jr. - "The Cost of Discipleship", 1996 June 23; 2045
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0813)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0481)
  - Geoffrey Wainwright - "Who Owns You?", 1996 June 30; 2046
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0814)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0482)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - Sermon Untitled, 1996 July 07; 2047
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0815)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0483)
  - Cynthia Lynnette Hale - "And We Know That", 1996 July 14; 2048
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0816)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0484)
  - William Willimon - "Life…through Death", 1996 July 21; 2049
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0817)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0485)
  - William Willimon - "Family Reunion", 1996 July 28; 2050
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0818)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0486)
  - William Willimon - "The Dark Adversary", 1996 August 04; 2051
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0819)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0487)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - Sermon Untitled, 1996 August 11; 2052
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0820)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0488)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - Sermon Untitled, 1996 August 18; 2053
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0821)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0489)
  - William Willimon - "You Are the Christ, Now What about Them?", 1996 August 25; 2054
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0822)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0490)
  - Nan Keohane - Opening Convocation, 1996 August 29; 2055
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0491)
    - Copy - VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0492)
  - William Willimon - "A Job or a Vocation?" Orientation, 1996 September 01; 2056
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0823)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0494)
  - William Willimon - "The Gothic Spirit", 1996 September 08; 2057
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0824)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0495)
  - William Willimon - "Our Kind of Crowd", 1996 September 15; 2058
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0825)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - Sermon Untitled, 1996 September 22; 2059
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0826)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0496)
  - William Willimon - "Words and Deeds", 1996 September 29; 2060
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0827)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0497)
  - William Willimon - "Taken and Given to Someone Else", 1996 October 06; 2061
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0828)
  - William Willimon - "The Perils of Rendering Unto Caesar", 1996 October 20; 2062
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0829)
  - William Willimon - "Living with Life's Incompleteness", 1996 October 27; 2063
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0830)
  - Gregory Edelstein - "Save Your People, Lord…", 1996 November 10; 2064
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0831)
  - William Willimon - "God, the Thief", 1996 November 17; 2065
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0832)
  - Charles Adams - "The Humanity of God", 1996 November 24; 2066
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0833)
  - William Willimon - "Where Is God?", 1996 December 01; 2067
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0834)
  - Hans J. Hillerbrand - "The Freedom of Honesty", 1996 December 08; 2068
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0835)
  - Gerald L. Wilson - "I and Thou: Inc., Ltd., Blessed", 1996 December 15; 2069
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0836)
  - William Willimon - "Unto Us", 1996 December 22; 2070
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0837)
  - Ian Williams - "The Light and Darkness Following Christmas", 1996 December 29; 2071
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0838)
  - Peter Gomes - "We Are the Gentiles", 1997 January 05; 2072
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0839)
  - Richard Lischer - "The River", 1997 January 12; 2073
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0840)
  - William Willimon - "The Dangers of Going to Church", 1997 January 19; 2074
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0841)
  - William Willimon - "A Political Joke", 1997 January 26; 2075
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0842)
  - William Willimon - "The Teacher", 1997 February 02; 2076
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0843)
  - William Willimon - "That He Might Bring Us to God", 1997 February 16; 2077
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0844)
  - Mark Michael - "Bearing the Cross", 1997 February 23; 2078
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0845)
  - Lenten Meditation and Music, 1997; 2079
    - Original audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1151)
  - William Willimon - "Fools for Christ", 1997 March 02; 2080
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0846)
  - Christine Smith - "Spreading and Moving the Table", 1997 March 09; 2081
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0847)
  - Michael A. Walrond, Jr. - "A Sincere Prayer Request", 1997 March 16; 2082
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0848)
  - William Willimon - "Suffered and Died", 1997 March 23; 2083
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0849)
  - William Willimon - "You Call This a Church?", 1997 April 06; 2084
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0850)
  - Dennis M. Campbell - "The Nature of Christian Leadership", 1997 April 20; 2085
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0851)
  - Barbara Brown Taylor - "Welcomed to Belong", 1997 April 27; 2086
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0852)
  - William Willimon - "Commanded to Love", 1997 May 04; 2087
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0853)
  - C. Jarrett Gray, Jr. - "Sent into the World", 1997 May 11; 2088
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0854)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "On Fire for God", 1997 May 18; 2089
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0855)
  - Jenny Jackson - Adams - "Show Me the Money", 1997 May 25; 2090
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0856)
  - James L. Travis III - "The Rhythm of Life", 1997 June 01; 2091
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0857)
  - Carol M. Noren - "On a Scale from One to Ten", 1997 June 08; 2092
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0858)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "When You Don't Understand", 1997 June 15; 2093
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0859)
  - William Willimon - "Does Jesus Care?", 1997 June 22; 2095
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0860)
  - William Willimon - "Get Up", 1997 June 29; 2094
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0861)
  - William Willimon - "On Not Meeting People's Needs at Church", 1997 July 06; 2096
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0862)
  - William Willimon - "Retirement: A Whole New Life", 1997 July 13; 2097
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0863)
  - William Willimon - "The Loving Shepherd", 1997 July 20; 2098
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0864)
  - William Willimon - "What Are You Looking For?", 1997 July 27; 2099
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0865)
  - William B. Lawrence - "When the Gifts of God Aren't Enough", 1997 August 03; 2100
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0866)
  - William Willimon - "A Tragic Family", 1997 August 10; 2101
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0867)
  - James C. Howell - "To Live a Fool and Die a Sage", 1997 August 17; 2102
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0868)
  - William Willimon - "An Uncontainable, yet Accessible God", 1997 August 24; 2103
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0869)
  - William Willimon - "Doers of the Word", 1997 August 31; 2104
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0870)
  - William Willimon - "Where Are You Headed?", 1997 September 07; 2105
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0871)
  - William Willimon - "The Journey", 1997 September 14; 2106
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0872)
  - William Willimon - "Unspectacular Faithfulness", 1997 September 28; 2107
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0873)
  - Charlene P. Kammerer - "Jesus' Final Request", 1997 October 05; 2108
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0874)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - "The Hidden Love of God", 1997 October 12; 2109
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0875)
  - Karen Westerfield Tucker - Sermon Untitled, 1997 October 19; 2110
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0876)
  - William Willimon - "When the Answers Don't Fit the Questions", 1997 October 26; 2111
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0877)
  - William Willimon - "A Most Radical Act", 1997 November 02; 2112
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0878)
  - William Willimon - "An Extravagant Lifestyle", 1997 November 09; 2113
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0879)
  - L. Gregory Jones - "Remembering Hope", 1997 November 16; 2114
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0880)
  - William Willimon - "Thy Kingdom Come", 1997 November 23; 2115
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0881)
  - William Willimon - "Lo, He Comes with Clouds Descending", 1997 November 30; 2116
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0882)
    - Copy - audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0883)
  - Peter J. Storey - "The Messenger of a New Day", 1997 December 07; 2117
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0884)
  - William Willimon - "Exile and Home", 1997 December 14; 2118
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0885)
  - William Willimon - "Imagination", 1997 December 21; 2119
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0886)
  - Michael Walrond - "Looking for Jesus in All the Wrong Places", 1997 December 28; 2120
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0887)
  - Stephen Bauman - Sermon Untitled, 1998 January 04; 2121
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0888)
  - William Willimon - "Your Ordination", 1998 January 11; 2122
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0889)
  - William Willimon - "Some Saw Glory", 1998 January 18; 2123
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0890)
  - William Willimon - "Contemptuous Familiarity", 1998 January 25; 2124
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0891)
  - William Willimon - "Sin Is a Byproduct of Worship", 1998 February 08; 2125
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0892)
  - Mark Michael - "Uncomfortable Trust", 1998 February 15; 2126
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0893)
  - Peter J. Gomes - "Before It's Too Late", 1998 February 22; 2127
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0894)
  - William Willimon - "How Can This Be?", 1998 February 28; 2128
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0895)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - "What a Friend We Have in Jesus", 1998 March 01; 2129
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0896)
  - William Willimon - "Satan: A Second Look", 1998 March 08; 2130
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0897)
  - Michael A. Walrond, Jr. - "Put on Your Jesus Lenses", 1998 March 22; 2131
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0898)
  - William Willimon - "Suicide Is Not a Private Matter", 1998 March 29; 2132
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0899)
  - William Willimon - "Shall We Dance?", 1998 April 05; 2133
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0900)
  - William Willimon - "Easter Is Large", 1998 April 12; 2134
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0901)
  - Dr. John R. Claypool IV - "Taking up for Thomas", 1998 April 19; 2135
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0902)
  - William Willimon - "A Song to Shake the World", 1998 April 26; 2136
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0903)
  - William Willimon - "Who Are These, Robed in White?", 1998 May 03; 2137
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0904)
  - William Willimon - "When the Outsiders Become Insiders", 1998 May 10; 2138
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0905)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "Do You Want to Be Healed?", 1998 May 17; 2139
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0906)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - Sermon Untitled, 1998 May 24; 2140
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0907)
  - William Willimon - "The Prevailing Spirit", 1998 May 31; 2141
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0908)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - "A Hope That Does Not Disappoint", 1998 June 07; 2142
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0909)
  - Michael A. Walrond, Jr. - "Transformed by Faith", 1998 June 14; 2143
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0910)
  - Ann I. Hoch - Sermon Untitled, 1998 June 21; 2144
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0911)
  - William Willimon - "Journeying with Jesus", 1998 June 28; 2145
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0912)
  - William Willimon - "As Those under Orders", 1998 July 05; 2146
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0913)
  - William Willimon - "The Call to Start Over", 1998 July 12; 2147
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0914)
  - Brett Webb - Mitchell - "From 'Doing for' to 'Being With'", 1998 July 19; 2148
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0915)
  - Elizabeth Achtemeier - "A Shocking Command", 1998 July 26; 2149
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0916)
  - William Willimon - "We Fools", 1998 August 02; 2150
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0917)
  - Kenneth L. Nelson - "Matters That Matter", 1998 August 09; 2151
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0918)
  - J. Lawrence McCleskey - "Whose Faithfulness?", 1998 August 16; 2152
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0919)
  - William Willimon - "What's in a Name?", 1998 August 23; 2153
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0920)
  - William Willimon - "Mind Your Manners", 1998 August 30; 2154
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0921)
  - William Willimon - "The Price of Discipleship", 1998 September 06; 2155
    - Original audiocassette (Box 36, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0922)
  - William Willimon - "Outrageous Parties", 1998 September 13; 2156
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0923)
  - William Willimon - "The Future and What to Do about It", 1998 September 20; 2157
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0924)
  - William Willimon - "A Great Distance between Us", 1998 September 27; 2158
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0925)
  - Richard Lischer - "Good Stewards", 1998 October 04; 2159
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0926)
  - William C. Gipson - "Keep Hope Alive", 1998 October 11; 2160
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0927)
  - William Willimon - "On Not Losing Heart", 1998 October 18; 2161
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0928)
  - William Willimon - "Amazing Grace", 1998 October 25; 2162
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0929)
  - William Willimon - "Saints, All of You", 1998 November 01; 2163
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0930)
  - Duke Chapel Choir - conducted by Kenneth L. Nelson, 1998 November 04; 2164
    - Original digital audio tape (Box 56, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 DAT-001)
  - William Willimon - "Apathy: Worst of Modern Sins", 1998 November 08; 2165
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0931)
  - William Willimon - "To Tell the Truth", 1998 November 15; 2166
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0932)
  - Kenneth L. Nelson - "Are You Ready to Give Thanks?", 1998 November 22; 2167
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0933)
  - Barbara Brown Taylor - "The Unexpected Messiah", 1998 November 29; 2168
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0934)
  - William Willimon - "An Earth-Shattering Event", 1998 December 06; 2169
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0935)
  - Jana Childers - "With Both Ears Tingling", 1998 December 13; 2170
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0936)
  - William Willimon - "Unto Us a Child", 1998 December 20; 2171
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0937)
  - William Willimon - "Christmas in Duke Chapel" UNC - TV, 1998; 2352
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0498)
    - Original betacam-sp videocassette (Box 56, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 BETA-0002)
  - William Willimon - "Blood in Bethlehem", 1998 December 27; 2172
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0938)
  - Martin Copenhaver - "The Giving Spirit", 1999 January 03; 2173
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0939)
  - William Willimon - "No Problem", 1999 January 10; 2174
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0940)
  - William C. Turner - "The Voice from the Bowels", 1999 January 17; 2175
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0941)
  - William Willimon - "Fishing with Jesus", 1999 January 24; 2176
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0942)
  - William Willimon - "The Word of the Cross", 1999 January 31; 2177
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0943)
  - Lenten Meditation and Music - conducted by Kenneth L. Nelson, 1999 February 01; 2178
    - Original audiocassette (Box 38, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-1152)
    - Original digital audio tape (Box 56, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 DAT-002)
  - William Willimon - Lenten Meditation, 1999 February 01; 2181
    - Original digital audio tape (Box 56, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 DAT-003)
  - William Willimon - "When in Our Music God Is Glorified", 1999 February 07; 2179
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0944)
  - Anthony Campolo - "The Dreams of the Elderly and the Visions of the Young", 1999 February 14; 2182
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0945)
  - James C. Howell - "We Say These Same Prayers Every Week", 1999 February 21; 2183
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0946)
  - William Willimon - "How Can This Be?", 1999 February 28; 2184
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0947)
  - Gary Lee - "Life in the In - Between", 1999 March 07; 2185
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0948)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "Seeing Is Believing", 1999 March 14; 2186
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0949)
  - Andy Langford - "Do You Believe This?", 1999 March 21; 2187
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0950)
  - William Willimon - "Ordinary Sin", 1999 March 28; 2188
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0951)
  - William Willimon - "Easter as an Earthquake" Easter Service 9:00 am, 1999 April 04; 2189
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0952)
  - William Willimon - "Easter as an Earthquake" Easter Service 11:00 am, 1999 April 04; 2190
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0953)
  - Kenneth L. Nelson - "Who Will Speak for Them?", 1999 April 11; 2191
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0954)
  - Peter J. Gomes - "Life Before Death", 1999 April 18; 2192
    - Original audiocassette (Box 37, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0955)
  - William Willimon - "Good Luck?", 1999 April 25; 2193